LEANDRO MARTIN ROLDAN

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

After working for many years in a telecommunications company, where I learned about working in teams, leadership, interpersonal relations, quality and customer satisfaction, and tasks set by goals, I decided to make a change in my professional career.

I discovered this amazing IT world, and I've already feel prepared to contribute to any project and to be part of the solution.

SKILLS

React.js
Next.js
Node.js
TypeScript
Leadeship
Express.js
Team work

JavaScript
PostgreSQL
Tailwind
Customer's service

EDUCATION

APX - Full Stack Web Developer

05/2021 - present day (finishing)

Universidad Siglo XXI - Bachelor of Business Administration 01/2019 - 03/2021

RECENT JOB EXPERIENCE

Analyst - Real Time Managment - Movistar Argentina 04/2021 - 12/2021

RESPONSIBILITIES

- \cdot To make sure that the customer's incoming calls flow is answered in due time.
- Requested actions to face everyday challenges.
- · Analysis of the causes of incoming calls diversions and their impact on the company metrics.

KEY ACCOMPLISHMENTS

- · To maintain the percentage of unanswered calls within the monthly goals.
- · To sustaine the productivity and sales in all the call centers, yet still ensuring the customer's quality service.

Team Leader - Call Center - Movistar Argentina 01/2013 - 03/2021

RESPONSIBILITIES

- \cdot To lead the members of my team in developing improvement plans to achieve monthly goals.
- · Research of new procedures for customer's service and solutions.
- · To contribute in the accomplishment of monthly goals, sales and customer's loyalty.

KEY ACCOMPLISHMENTS

- · Team efficiency, keeping the incoming calls flow regulated without wasting time.
- · Team quality, constantly achieving the customer's satisfaction goals.

LANGUAGES